{
    "id": "e0d9686da85640b88027a215dd7d94f6",
    "title": "For, To And So That",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She has moved to England ……………………… she can perfect her English.",
            "description": "So that is a conjunction used to express purpose. It goes before a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e12667a654c04e6b8fcdad7f764d2c3c"
        },
        {
            "question": "We send monthly reports ……………………… parents can assess the progress of their children.",
            "description": "So that is a conjunction used to express purpose. It goes before a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a9d7bc1fba9d4c37a89b1b70d8cc8e08"
        },
        {
            "question": "He came to Mumbai ……………………… for work.",
            "description": "We use the infinitive to express a person’s purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "to look",
                "for looking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3a8c7293d6c643a684f9371118ba0e04"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to Canada ………………………… my brother.",
            "description": "We use the infinitive to express a person’s purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "to see",
                "for seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8da706e8bedd4bb584ae2fdeb04ee281"
        },
        {
            "question": "Send the parcel express ………………………… they will get it before Saturday.",
            "description": "So that is a conjunction used to express purpose. It goes before a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "be5e96be131d4f3aaa759885991646d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to the college ……………………….. an interview with my professor.",
            "description": "We use for to talk about somebody’s purpose in doing something.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ddc348df88c74182b1454d341892b67a"
        },
        {
            "question": "A barometer is used ………………………. height above sea level.",
            "description": "We can use for to express the purpose of a thing especially when that thing is the subject of the clause.",
            "answers": [
                "to measure",
                "for measuring",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "65a8f1a897a945f8b9a4ede007220b0e"
        },
        {
            "question": "We use a thermometer ………………………. temperature.",
            "description": "When the clause has a person as subject, we use an infinitive to express the purpose of a thing.",
            "answers": [
                "to measure",
                "for measuring"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "88052dec5e294acd9051f952dfd68d4b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s have a short break ……………………. lunch.",
            "description": "For is a preposition indicating purpose. It goes before a noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1c937864f28d4740bf527eeea34b8970"
        },
        {
            "question": "Is there anything that I need to get ……………………….. the party?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7c7b5650826547b48ffdd757400d2940"
        },
        {
            "question": "We left early …………………………… we wouldn’t get stuck in the traffic.",
            "description": "So that is a conjunction used to express purpose. It goes before a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "so that",
                "in order that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ad3d628d5e504419864bd9f291040511"
        },
        {
            "question": "I worked hard ……………………….. I might pass the test.",
            "description": "The conjunctions so that and in order that are both used to express purpose. ",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "in order that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a1a702af02d74e18aa453b1d607d618c"
        }
    ]
}